Register of the Stanford University Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies Collection, 1954-1965
Hoover Institution Archives
- January 1958
  - Venezuela (3 envelopes) one containing late, uncatalogued, and unclassified material
  - International (Box 124.)
- February 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 124.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia (Box 125.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 126.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 127.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- March 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 127.)
  - Bolivia (Box 128.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 129.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 130.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (6 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama (Box 131.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 132.)
- April 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 132.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 133.)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 134.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua (Box 135.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 136.)
- May 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 136.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 137.)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 138.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal, (6 envelopes) (Box 139.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay (Box 140.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- June 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 141.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 142.)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica (2 envelopes, one containing Pan-American Lacsa material)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador (Box 143.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama (Box 144.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International (2 envelopes plus one folder: Contract between Yacimientos Petroliferos Fiscales and Pan American International Oil Co. (Box 145.)
- July 1958
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 145.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 146.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes) (Box 147.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 148.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (Box 149.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 150.)
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- August 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 150.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes) (Box 151.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 152.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 153.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 154.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- September 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 155.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 156.)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 157.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes) (Box 158.)
  - Nicaragua (Box 159.)
  - Panama
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay (Box 160.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- October 1958
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 161.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes) (Box 162.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador (Box 163.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (2 envelopes) (Box 164.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 165.)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- November 1958
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 165.)
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 166.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 167.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti (Box 168.)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (6 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua (Box 169.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 170.)
- December 1958
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 170.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 171.)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 172.)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 173.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Spain (Box 174.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- January 1959
  - Argentina (3 envelopes, one containing Boletin Bibliografico and Revista de Comunicacisnes (Box 175.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes) (Box 176.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (9 envelopes) (Box 177.)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 178.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala (Box 179.)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (Box 180.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras (Box 181.)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- February 1959
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 181.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia (Box 182.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (8 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 183.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 184.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal (Box 185.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 186.)
  - West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- March 1959
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 186.)
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 187.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 188.)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti (Box 189.)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama (Box 189.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 190.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies
  - International
- April 1959
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 191.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica (Box 192.)
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador (Box 193.)
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (Box 194.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela (Box 195.)
  - West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- May 1959
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 195.)
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 196.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 197.)
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 198.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 199.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes)
  - West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- June 1959
  - Argentina, (5 envelopes) (Box 200.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil (June and July)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 201.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba (4 envelopes, one June and July) (Box 202.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama (Box 203.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Uruguay (Box 204.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- July 1959
  - Argentina (7 envelopes, 4 containing La Nación) (Box 205.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 206.)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (7 envelopes)
  - Cuba (Box 207.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay (Box 208.)
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Uruguay (Box 209.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- August 1959
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 210.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 211.)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador (Box 212.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal (Box 213.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela (Box 214.)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International
- September 1959
  - Argentina (7 envelopes, 4 containing La Nacion and one containing La Prensa) (Box 214.)
  - Bolivia (Box 215.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 216.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 217.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes) (Box 218.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International (Box 219.)
- October 1959
  - Argentina (9 envelopes, 5 containing La Nacion and 2 containing La Prensa) (Box 219.)
  - Argentina (4 envelopes, 2 containing La Nacion and 2 containing La Prensa (Box 220.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 221.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 222.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 223.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico (Box 224.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 225.)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- November 1959
  - Argentina (8 envelopes, 3 containing La Nacion and 3 containing La Prensa) (Box 226.)
  - Bolivia
  - Bolivia (Box 227.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 228.)
  - Cuba (Box 229.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 230.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico (Box 231.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela (Box 232.)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International
- December 1959
  - Argentina (Box 232.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 233.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 234.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras (Box 235.)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 236.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 237.)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International
- January 1960
  - Argentina (Box 237.)
  - Bolivia
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes) (Box 238.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 239.)
  - Cuba (Box 240.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 241.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal and Spain
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 242.)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes) (Box 243.)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- February 1960
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 243.)
  - Bolivia
  - Bolivia (Box 244.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Colombia (Box 245.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 246.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti (Box 247.)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal (Box 248.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 249.)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International
  - International (Box 250.)
- March 1960
  - Argentina (5 envelopes, 3 of which contain La Prensa) (Box 250.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes) (Box 251.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 252.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 253.)
  - Cuba (contains Boletin Cultural) (Box 254.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico (Box 255.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 256.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 257.)
  - West Indies, (3 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 258.)
- April 1960
  - Argentina (4 envelopes, 2 of which contain La Prensa) (Box 258.)
  - Argentina (Box 259.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes) (Box 260.)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 261.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador (Box 262.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru (3 envelopes, one of which contains La Brea y Parinas) (Box 263.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (4 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Spain (Box 264.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 265.)
  - West Indies, (3 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 266.)
- May 1960
  - Argentina (2 envelopes, one of which contains La Prensa) (Box 266.)
  - Argentina (contains La Prensa) (Box 267.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Chile (Box 268.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 269.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (3 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 270.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes) (Box 271.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - West Indies, (4 envelopes) (Box 272.)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- June 1960
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 272.)
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 273.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Chile (Box 274.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba (5 envelopes, one of which contains Diario de Las Americas and another which contains Revolución)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 275.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes) (Box 276.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 277.)
  - West Indies, (4 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- July 1960
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 278.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes) (Box 279.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba (7 envelopes) (one of which contains CIA Monitoring Report, one of which contains Diario de Las Americas, and one of which contains El Avace Criselo) (Box 280.)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 281.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama (Box 282.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela (Box 283.)
  - West Indies, (3 envelopes)
  - West Indies, Netherlands
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- August 1960
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 283.)
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 284.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 285.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 286.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti, (2 envelopes)
  - Honduras (Box 287.)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 288.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - West Indies (August and September)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International
  - International, (8 envelopes) (Box 289.)
- September 1960
  - Argentina, (5 envelopes) (Box 290.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 291.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba (5 envelopes, one containing AVANCE - September-October) (Box 292.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes) (Box 293.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua (Box 294.)
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 295.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - Table of Contents 1960
  - Commentary Book Shelf 1960
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 296.)
- October 1960
  - Argentina, (5 envelopes) (Box 296.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes) (Box 297.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 298.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba (5 envelopes, one of which contains CIA Reports and one which contains Vance and Times of Havana)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 299.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 300.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama, (3 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 301.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- November 1960
  - Argentina, (5 envelopes) (Box 302.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 303.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (7 envelopes) (Box 304.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador (Box 305.)
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes) (Box 306.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Hondures (October - November)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras
  - French West Indies (Box 307.)
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- December 1960
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 307.)
  - Argentina (Box 308.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes) (Box 309.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes) (Box 310.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 311.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay (Box 312.)
  - Venezuela (4 envelopes, one containing official presidential proclamations, another containing Armed Forces' publications from 1958-1960)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies (Box 313.)
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- January 1961
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 313.)
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 314.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 315.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba (7 envelopes, one containing CIA Reports, another containing Copley, Avanee, and Cuban Info. Service) (Box 316.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes) (Box 317.)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama (Box 318.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 319.)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 320.)
- February 1961
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 320.)
  - Argentina (Box 321.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (6 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 322.)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba (3 envelopes, one containing a Cuban Press Survey and another containing Avance and The William Wieland Case) (Box 323.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 324.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)